const initialState = {
    quiz: [
		{
		  question: 'Where is Taj Mahal Located?',
		  choices: ['Mumbai', 'Agra', 'New Delhi', 'None of these'],
		  correct: 2,
		},
		{
		  question: 'What color does yellow and green make?',
		  choices: ['Lime', 'Ocean mist', 'Maroon', 'Tangerine'],
		  correct: 1,
		},
		{
		  question: 'The hottest planet in the solar system?',
		  choices: ['Mercury', 'Venus', 'Mars', 'Jupiter'],
		  correct: 1,
		},
		{
		  question: "'www' stands for:",
		  choices: ['World Wide Web', 'World Wide Wares', 'World Wide Wait', 'World Wide War'],
		  correct: 1,
		},
		{
		  question: 'Which is the first smart city in world?',
		  choices: ['New Jersey', 'Seoul', 'Vatican City', 'California'],
		  correct: 2,
		},
		{
		  question: 'Where is Gateway of India Located?',
		  choices: ['Mumbai', 'Chennai', 'New Delhi', 'Hyderabad'],
		  correct: 1,
		},
		{
		  question: 'Which one of the following ports is the oldest port in India?',
		  choices: ['Mumbai Port', 'Chennai Port', 'Kolkata Port', 'Vishakhapatnam Port'],
		  correct: 2,
		},
		{
		  question: 'Which is the tallest waterfalls in the world ?',
		  choices: ['Jog Falls', 'Tugela Falls', 'Angel Falls', 'Victoria Falls'],
		  correct: 3,
		},
		{
		  question: "Which of the following is called 'the Land of Rising Sun' ?",
		  choices: ['India', 'China', 'U.S.A', 'Japan'],
		  correct: 4,
		},
		{
		  question: 'Which is the southernmost point of India?',
		  choices: ['Siachin', 'Indira Point', 'Thiruvananthapuram', 'Kanyakumari'],
		  correct: 2,
		},
		{
		  question: 'For which of the following disciplines is Nobel Prize awarded?',
		  choices: ['Literature, Peace and Economics', 'Physics and Chemistry', 'Physiology or Medicine', 'All of the above'],
		  correct: 4,
		},
		{
		  question: 'The United Nations Organization has its Headquarters at ',
		  choices: ['Bali', 'Hague', 'New York, USA', 'Washington DC'],
		  correct: 3,
		},
		{
		  question: ' Objects at the surface of water can be viewed from a submarine under water by using which instrument ?',
		  choices: ['Stethescope', 'Periscope', 'Kaleidoscope', 'Telescope'],
		  correct: 2,
		},
		{
		  question: "Who created the famous Rock Garden of Chandigarh ?",
		  choices: ['Gaudi', 'Saarinen', 'Krishnarao Jaisim', 'Nek Chand'],
		  correct: 4,
		},
		{
		  question: "NASAâ€™s most famous space telescope goes by the name?",
		  choices: ['Muble Satellite Telescope', ' Hubble Space Telescope', 'Humble Space Telescope', 'Galaxy Satellite Telescope'],
		  correct: 2,
		},
		{
		  question:	"At room temperature, which is the only metal that is in liquid form?",
		  choices: ['Iron', 'Aluminum', 'Mercury', 'Silver'],
		  correct: 3,
		},
		{
		  question: 'The tropic of cancer does not pass through which of these Indian states ?',
		  choices: ['Madhya Pradesh', 'West Bengal', 'Rajasthan', 'Odisha'],
		  correct: 4,
		},
		{
		  question: 'In which of the following festivals are boat races a special feature?',
		  choices: ['Rongali Bihu ', 'Onam', 'Pongal', 'Navratri'],
		  correct: 2,
		},
		{
		  question: 'The blue colour of the clear sky is due to',
		  choices: ['Diffraction of light', 'Dispersion of light', 'Reflection of light', 'Refraction of light'],
		  correct: 2,
		},
	]
}

const reducer = (state= initialState, action) => {

	return state;
	
}

export default reducer;